All right. Well, so let's Should we do
any more of these or should we just get
to the questions?
>> Can I can I do just I I'm probably the
only person who's interested in this,
but I I've given I I gave I should say
two uh interviews over the weekend to
Greek outlets. Um a Greek uh colonel
assigned to NATO was arrested and and
charged with espionage for spying for
China. This is highly highly unusual in
Greece.
>> Not that somebody's been arrested for
espionage. That happens quite
frequently. It's almost always spying
for the Russians. What's unusual is that
this was the Chinese.
>> Um there is very little there there was
very little evidence when I was still in
the game that the Russians I'm sorry
that the Chinese gave two shits about
NATO. They didn't care about NATO. Now
apparently they care very much about
NATO because they were trying to
intercept NATO's communications and to
decrypt it. This guy, he's a colonel and
as I said he immediately confessed. He
said that he took an undisclosed trip to
China a year ago. The Chinese recruited
him there. They've they were giving him
5,000 to 15,000 for every classified
document he brought out. He communicated
with them on a separate cell phone,
completely unencrypted, terrible trade
craft. Nothing was done clandestinely,
just right out in the open. And um this
guy's going to spend much of the rest of
his life in prison.
>> Wow. Anyway, it brings the Chinese into
into an espionage story in Europe where
they otherwise haven't been before.
>> So, we're going to see more of this,
>> I think. So, yeah.
>> Um well, before we move on, um some
speaking of Europe, a couple of top
ranking European officials are dropping
like flies due to the EP their Epstein
connections.
>> That's right.
>> In France and in, uh Belgium.
>> Um what do you know, any thoughts? Um,
yeah, I think that this is going to
start to spread. And ironically, the
United States appears to be the only
place where nobody's taking these
Epstein revelations seriously. I said
this last week, I'm going to say it
again as I pull this little piece of
lint off my sweater that I can't seem to
get a hold of. But, uh, I said last
week, this could bring down the, uh, the
Kirst government. Now there there are
two different pieces of evidence
indicating that former Prince Andrew and
Peter Mandelson both gave um both gave
Epstein classified documents from the
British Ministry of Defense. If so, that
would be a violation of this the um
Official Secrets Act,
>> which in in the United States would be a
violation of the Espionage Act. uh
they're far tougher than we are uh with
these these violations, these classified
document violations. And not only is
Peter Manderson likely going to prison,
but this could be enough to cause
backbenchers in the Labor Party to force
a vote on leadership. It could be the
end of Kier Starmer in the next couple
of weeks.
>> It does kind of feel like that. Um yeah,
he has the smell he has the smell of the
of the Liz Trust cabbage on him.
>> I I was going to say the same thing. He
He's lasted slightly longer than the
cabbage, but not much.
>> No. Um, wow. And uh Yeah. And I mean,
and I guess now it's official. We're
never going to see the other half of the
Epstein files.
>> I don't know, man. I mean, people I I I
spent a good bit of the last week going
through the Epstein files, and I found
several John Brennan related documents
that I'm going to try to make some hay
over, but um I don't know, man. Three
three million documents. It's people are
still going through them and there are
millions left. I mean, the guy was like
the guy never got off email.
>> It's incredible. But another thing too,
Ted,
even though the statute of limitations
has expired for just about every crime
committed against the the victims, uh,
the child victims here in the United
States, um, that's not to say that the
people who were engaged with Epstein and
the people committing those crimes
shouldn't be publicly shamed, that they
shouldn't be ruined, you know, like
Peter Mandelen,
who's of course a UK national, but you
know, the the general counsel for for
Goldman Sachs and all these billionaire
businessmen who thought it was perfectly
okay to associate with a child rapist.
They need to be called to account.
>> Illuminous Katar, thanks for the 20
Australian dollars. How will the current
release of the files impact the
USIsraeli relationship with it now
seeming more obvious it was a Mossad
honeypot operation.
>> Totally.
>> Wondering if you could talk more about
your experience in Israel.
Yeah, it was totally an Israeli honeypot
uh operation and I don't think anything
is going to change. Nothing. I mean, how
I've been out there shouting from the
rooftops that the Israelis, you know,
spy on us. Uh Alan Dersowitz calls me
names and the the Israeli foreign
minister's political director called me
a noted anti-semite because of it. And
it's true. They're still out there
spying on us.
Question for both of us from Pink Lady.
Do we believe what Steven Greer has said
about the government hiding evidence
about aliens? John, can you send me a
signed photo of yourself before you're
too famous?
>> Sure, of course. I I have to find one.
Uh what was the first part of the
question?
>> Um Steven Greer, Aliens.
>> Uh yeah. Um people have asked me that
over the years. Um, I don't know to tell
you the truth. I mean, if there is
evidence, it's being tightly held at the
Pentagon, but uh I honestly
>> What do you think about those um like 5
years ago when the US Air Force released
those um videos of uh UFOs?
>> Mhm. There was one that was leaked uh in
September that is dramatic. It's it's
two uh F-18s
uh following a UFO, an orb, a silver orb
off the coast of Yemen, and they're
talking about it back and forth. The
camera never leaves the orb. And they're
given permission to fire at it. It was a
Hellfire missile, Sidewinder missile,
one or the other. And you see the
missile hit the thing and the missile
just bounces off and the orb just
changes direction by by 90 degrees and
just keeps flying. Incredible.
>> I mean, look, there's definitely
evidence. Is there proof? There's not
proof, but there's evidence.
>> Somebody asked if at the CIA uh we we
viewed our recruited sources as traitors
and held them in contempt.
>> That's an interesting question. And the
answer is absolutely not. You know, we
really really believed that we were the
good guys.
>> And so if we were able to recruit
somebody and make them one of the good
guys, we were all one big happy family.
There were there were a couple of
sources that I recruited who in normal
life I would not be friends with, right?
We would not we would not have had
contact. They were scumbags. In one case
they were he was a killer like a just a
coldblooded
stone cold killer. Um
but seven of the nine people that I
recruited over the years I would love to
be friendly with them. I
>> don't So you didn't have that sense of
like sort of like, you know, like the
person who has an affair with a married
person and then they they're like, well,
you know, they could they could do this
to me too someday, right? I mean, you
didn't have that sort of
>> Oh, sure. Sure. And that's what vetting
is all about. So, you know, you've got
to polygraph them. You have to what we
call operationally test them. I I'll
tell you I there was this one source
that I had who I really really liked and
because he was from an enemy country, he
was recruited under under special
circumstances. Well, he was so reliable,
I wanted to move him over to normal
circumstances. It's a paperwork
exercise. And as part of that paperwork
exercise, I had to operationally test
him. So I I put a large surveillance
team on him as he left his place of work
and uh and they followed him to the
meeting site and the the head of the
security the head of the surveillance
team kept calling me saying he's doing
this, he's doing that, he's doing this,
he's doing that. At one point he got in
a taxi, um had the taxi just pull over
on the side of a of a an eight lane
highway and then he ran across all eight
lanes, climbed over the median, got in
the cab on the other side and went the
opposite direction and then got on the
subway and came to the meeting. It was a
terrific, it was very very provocative
in terms of of you know the surveillance
detection route. So when he got there, I
knew exactly what he had done, but I
said, "Did you do a surveillance
detection route on your way here?" And
he said, "Yeah." I said, "Okay, walk me
through it and tell me what you did."
And he told me like to to a move exactly
what he did. And we were able to move
him straight into the Yes, we can trust
him camp.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. If he doesn't get run over.
>> I've actually run into sources twice. uh
once at at an airport and uh and once on
the street and it was you know years
well in one case it was it was four
years after I left the agency in the
other case it was you know 20 years
after I left the agency.
>> Can you just nod or can you say hi?
>> They came up to me. I wasn't really
paying attention and they came up to me
and it was big bear hugs and oh my god
how are you doing? And one guy said I
can't believe YOU SPEAK ENGLISH.
I can't believe it.
>> That's funny. He didn't know. Um Josh
Buck, are there people still actually
working on tracking and removing spies
in the United States? Is it possible to
achieve? Will we ever be free from
foreign control?
>> So, the the FBI's counterintelligence
division, that's literally all they do
is to try to root out spies and to
remove them or prosecute them. Um, it's
an ongoing never-ending job because more
and more spies are coming here every
day. There are more spies in Washington
DC than anywhere else in the world. And
um it's not possible to to win to root
them all out. Unless you want to be
North Korea,
>> it's whack-a-ole.
>> It's whack-a-ole. Yeah.
>> Bicycle Pro 1212345.
Uh, thanks for the uh $8 donation. Um,
ever do spy work with the Aussies? would
be interested in knowing what you
thought about our intel service if you
ever did.
>> Um I I never did anything operationally
with the Australians. Um I briefed them
a number of times. We have you know
they're five eyes countries so it they
they're literally sitting there in the
building. Um they their primary focus is
as you might expect is China and that
was never my thing. So worked in
proximity with them but almost never
directly. They're quite good. They're
quite a good service. Very good service.